Guide to the Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2018
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2018
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2018
14-16-3477
Cornell University.Dept. of Government.
7.3 cubic ft.
Honors Theses
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Honors theses arranged by year.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Honors theses arranged by year.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University.Dept. of Government.; Cornell University.Class of 1991.; Cornell University.Class of 1992.; Cornell University.Class of 1993.; Cornell University.Class of 1994.; Cornell University.Class of 1995.; Cornell University.Class of 1996.; Cornell University.Class of 1997.; Cornell University.Class of 1998.; Cornell University.Class of 1999.; Cornell University.Class of 2000.; Cornell University.Class of 2001.; Cornell University.Class of 2002.; Cornell University.Class of 2003.; Cornell University.Class of 2004.; Cornell University.Class of 2005.; Cornell University.Class of 2006.; Cornell University.Class of 2007.; Cornell University.Class of 2008.; Cornell University.Class of 2009.; Cornell University.Class of 2010.; Cornell University.Class of 2011.; Cornell University.Class of 2012.; Cornell University.Class of 2013.; Cornell University.Class of 2014.; Cornell University.Class of 2015.; Cornell University.Class of 2016.; Cornell University.Class of 2017.; Cornell University.Class of 2018.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
  -
- The Cyclical Nature of Airline Antitrust Policy, 1991-05-22; Einhorn, David (Box 1)
- From the Bottom Up: Business/Government Relations in the U.S. and Japan, 1991-05; Pempel, Aaron (Box 1)
- "Towards an Expanding Europe: EFTA's Rush and Resistance", 1992; Dylla, Bronwyn (Box 1)
- "Utopia Unbound: The Social and Political Theory of Herbert Marcuse", 1992-04-13; Braun, Martin Z. (Box 1)
- "Representation for the Black Electorate: The Search for Political Equality Reaches a Fork in the Road", 1993-04-12; Baylin, Noah (Box 1)
- "The European Convention on Human Rights: A Study of Normative Enforcement", 1993; Tseng, Elaine (Box 1)
  Spring
- "Public Policies, Private Remedies: Product Liability, the Consumer Product Safety Commission, and the Politics of Injury", 1994-04-11; Gordon, C. Sanford (Box 1)
- "The Perpetuation of an Inefficient System: The Relationship Between School Finance Inequities and the Political Process in Lake County, Illinois", 1994-04-10; Wiggins, Michael J. (Box 1)
- "Lenin and the Ethics of Terror", 1994-04-11; Wulf, Steven J. (Box 1)
- "The "Success" of West German Denazification: A Comparative Analysis of West Germany, East Germany and Austria's Value Change in the Post-War Era", 1995-04-10; Gould, Erica Ruth (Box 1)
- "Martial Species: Understanding Sikh Ethno-Nationalism", 1995; Sekhon, Nirej S. (Box 1)
- "The Domestic Implications of Exchange Decontrol: A Case Study", 1996-04; Bernstein, David L. (Box 1)
- "Misdeal: How the Federal Government Unintentionally Catalyzed the Greatest Proliferation of Legal Casino Gambling in United States History", 1996-04-15; Goldin, Nicholas (Box 1)
- "Russia's Foreign Policy Paradox: Democracy as Anti-Western", 1996-04-15; Moseley, Alec (Box 1)
- "Machine Politics: Partisan Uses of Databases and the Internet", 1997-04-18; Goodhart, Noah J. (Box 1)
- "The Commodity of Life: Politics, Packaging, and Patenting of Genetic Science", 1997-04; Little, Eric (Box 1)
- "The Death of the Subject and Its Political Consequences", 1998-11-23; James, Richard (Box 1)
- "Prospects for Peace: The Political Context of Northern Ireland's Good Friday Agreement: An Analysis", 1999-04; Cope, Emily T. (Box 1)
- "Stemming Nuclear Proliferation: The Role of Expectations in a State's Decision Calculus", 2000-04-17; Singh, Sonali (Box 1)
- "Conflict Resolution in Enduring Rivalries: The Importance of Political Shocks", 2001-04-16; Aycock, Jamie (Box 4)
- "Institutional Bias: A Case Study of Plea Bargaining in Orleans Parish, Louisiana", 2001-04-16; Bankole, Olufunke Grace (Box 1)
- "The Art of Rhetorical Manipulation: Legitimating China's Economic Reforms in Official Discourse", 2001-04-16; Huang, Reyko (Box 1)
- "The Political Role of Religion in America: a Tocquevillian Perspective", 2001-04-18; Lim, Grace (Box 1)
- "Native Hawaiian Sovereignty: The Tragedy of Displacement", 2001-04; Minami, David A. (Box 1)
- "An Institutional Theory of Third Party Politics", 2002-04; Gershoff, Amy Rachel (Box 1)
- "Refinements to the Opportunistic Political Business Cycle Theory", 2002-04-18; Hing, Byron (Box 1)
- "Sexuality, Family, and Citizenship: An Intervention in Queer and Feminist Theory", 2002-04-18; Romero, Adam Phillip (Box 1)
- "No Buses in Bugtussle: Regionalism and the Failure of Fuel Taxation Policy in America", 2003-04-17; Angevine, Christopher (Box 1)
- "The Partisan Politics of Ex-Felon Disenfranchisement Laws", 2003-04; Conn, Jason Belmont (Box 1)
- "Economic Shift and Political Fallout: The Impact of Liberalization on Indian Politics", 2003-04-17; Karunakaran, Ganesh (Box 1)
- "Israeli Military Actions and Diversionary Behavior", Fall 2003; Kronfol, Hania (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "Gulag: A Trauma Archipelago", 2003-04; Kusa, Livia (Box 2)
- "The Two Faces of International Assistance: NATO and EU Involvement in Central and Eastern Europe", 2003-04; Petrova, Tsveta (Box 2)
- "Institutionalization in a Period of Prisoners' Rights Retrenchment: States' Responses to Lewis v. Casey", 2004-04; Galardy, Jo Anne (Box 2)
- "Animal Rights and Human Morality: Achieving Normative Consensus through a Contractualist Deliberative Framework", 2004-04; Grossman, Bradley Dax (Box 2)
- "The Solicitor General's Political Role as Amicus Curiae in the United States Supreme Court", 2004-04-22; Schartz, Brian (Box 2)
- "Deprived of Rights, Detained, and Deported: Unaccompanied Alien Children in the United States 1984-2004", 2004-04-26; Levine, Alison Rose (Box 2)
- "Settlement and Paralysis: The Split Personality of Ethnic Conflict in the Post-Soviet States", 2004-04-19; Shulman, Ilya (Box 2)
- "The Effects of Employment and Unemployment on Voting Preferences in the 2004 Presidential Election", 2005-04-18; Hausberg, William (Box 2)
- "Strategies of Democracy Promotion: Are Non-Governmental Organizations Effective?", 2005-04-18; Levy, Julia (Box 2)
- "The Christian Right, The Christian Left, and United States Foreign Policy", 2005-04; Parker, Daniel (Box 2)
- "From Strauss to Lacan, From Intention to Desire: Two Methods of Reading Through Machiavelli's 'The Prince'", 2005; Stanish, Michael (Box 2)
- "Fighting Justices: Personal Animosity and Decision-Making on the United States Supreme Court", 2005; Suh, Catherine (Box 2)
- "Radical Reform: Institutional Resistance to the Prison Litigation Reform Act", 2006; Nagy, Nathan (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "What's on TV Tonight? An Analysis of the Television Campaign of Advertisements of Male or Female Political Candidates", 2007; Cassorla, Michelle (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "Accompanying the King: Building a Democratic Governance State in Morocco", 2007; Ng, Andrew (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "Contested Fields: Agrarian Discourse in Contemporary Farm Debates", 2007; Saltzman, Amy (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "Iran's Quest for Nuclear Power and Status: Prestige Motives in Nuclear Proliferation", 2007; Testa, Paul (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "The Price Tag for Civil Rights: 'Pay as You Go' Prisoner Access to the Courts", 2008; Beekman, Jason (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "Squaring the Circle: State Capitalism and Singapore's Government-Linked Companies" (2 copies), 2008; Hong, Junchen (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "The Online Israeli-Palestinian Conflict: How Authority Shapes Public Spheres on the Internet", 2008; Stern, Jason (Box 2, Folder 9)
- "Performing Gender at the Podium: 'Women's Language' in Gubernatorial Debates", 2009; White, Ariel (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "The American Response to the International Criminal Court: The Application of International Relations Theory and Subsequent Implications", 2003; Winkelman Jaime (Box 2)
- "Face Value and Foreign Policy: China and the Taiwan Strait Crises, 1995-1999", 2005; Quek, Ch-Yuan Kaiy (Box 2)
- "From Provision to Power: Challenges to the State from Religious Non-Governmental Organizations in the Middle East", 2008; Kiferbaum, David (Box 2)
- "What Rocks The Vote: Explaining State Variation of Young Voter Turnout Rates", 2008; Lippman, Julia (Box 2)
- "The Vicissitudes of United States Policy toward North Korea Policy and the Sources of United States Foreign Policy", 2008; Kim, Sung Wook (Box 2)
- "Compromise and Controversy: The Perplexing Origins of No Child Left Behind", 2008; Rubin, Leonard (Box 2)
- "Cross-Party Presidential Tickets: Frequently Considered, Never Realized, but Formidable Nonetheless", 2009; Goldstein, Josh (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Mr. Smith Hates Washington: Cultural Intimacy, Savior Citizens, and the Politics of Naivety in Modern America", 2009; Freilich, Ari (Box 3)
- "Pragmatic Policy Adjustment in Congress Following Landslide Presidential Defeats: The Republicans 1964-1966 and the Democrats 1972-1974", 2009; Campbell, Jeremy D. (Box 3)
- "A World of Financial Models", 2009; de Lencquesaing, Luis-Francois (Box 3)
- "Unexpected Presidents and Their Legacies in the Twentieth Century: Patterns in 'Accidental' Succession", 2009; Pavel, Alexandra (Box 3)
- "Assessing the Breakdown of FTAA Negotiations as a Result of Ideational Incompatibility: A Statistical Analysis", 2009; Larin, Roxana (Box 3)
- "Russia and the European Union: Identity and Policy in the Post-Soviet Space", 2009; Eltsefon, Larissa (Box 3)
- "The Religionsmiths: An Examination of Neoconservatism's Engagement with the Tree Monotheistic Faiths", 2009; Weinstein, Aaron Q. (Box 3)
- "Rethinking Migration and Security: The Indispensability of Legalization in the Quest to Make America Safer", 2009; Snider, Madeline Rose (Box 3)
- "Free to Submit: A Foucauldian Analysis of Women's Rights and the New Modern in Morocco", 2009; Robertson, Cassandra (Box 3)
- "Enemies in All Those Whom You have Injured" Economic Ties, Transformation, and Political Protest, 2009; Bertorelli, Robert (Box 3)
- "A Nuclear Iran: Who Fears It? Who Welcomes It? An Analysis of the Security Council's Response to Iran's Nuclear Program", 2009; Slevin, Maury (Box 3)
- "From Subject to Participant? The Development of German Political Culture in the Postwar Era", 2009; Grynberg, Noah (Box 3)
- "The 'Faithful Voter': Catholics, the Democratic Party, and United States Presidential Elections Since 1952", 2009; McGowan, Virginia (Box 3)
- "Women, Health, and Power: Examining the Relationship Between Women's Healthcare and Women's Representation in Sub-Saharan Africa", 2010; Aldric, Alma Isavel Arnedo (Box 3)
- "The United States of America and the Islamic Republic of Iran", 2010; Aviral, Neha (Box 3)
- "The Politics of Corrections: Partisanship and Incarceration at the State Level, 1980-2002", 2010; Bilmes, Elie (Box 3)
- "Path Dependency and Suthoritarian Legacies: Institutions, Human Rights, and Chile's Transition to Democracy", 2010; Brody, Kimberly (Box 3)
- "Systematic Sexual Violence during War: An Analysis of Violence against Women in Israel/Palestine, Sri Lanka, and Sudan", 2010; Bronsther, Carrie (Box 3)
- "Fleeing Persecution? The Politics of Immigration and Asylum Policymaking in the United States and Canada", 2010; Curran, Elizabeth (Box 3)
- "Foreign Aid in the National Interest: A Model of Bilateral Development Assistance in Sub-Saharan Africa", 2010; Cutting, Isabel (Box 3, Folder 2)
- "Clever Humility: An Analysis of the Importance of Cultural Artifice in Iranian Society and Politics", 2010; Dastgir, Donial (Box 3, Folder 3)
- "Midterm Loss: Examining the Relationship between Presidential Agendas and Midterm Election Outcomes", 2010; Desai, Rahul (Box 3)
- "Not Just About Drugs: The United States War on Drugs, Plan Colombia, and the Merida Initiative", 2010; Gomez-Herrera, Felipe (Box 3)
- "The Psychological Construction of the SOviet Threat: A Study in the Making of United States Soviet Policy from 1945 to 1947", 2010; Hart, William (Box 3)
- "Unity in Autonomy", 2010; Koh, Junrong Keith (Box 3)
- "Paradox Confirmed: A Test of Daniel Drezner's Theory on the Efficacy of Economic Statecraft in International Relations with New Data from 1998-2008", 2010; Masanoff, Rian (Box 3)
- "Systematic Violence and Regional Human Rights Systems", 2010; Meyer, Kate (Box 3)
- "Containing the Atom: Paul Nitze and the Tradition of Non-Use of Nuclear Weapons", 2010; Reid, Pauly (Box 3)
- "United States Foreign Policy Toward the Cold War Middle East: An Analytic Narrative (1948-1973)", 2010; Pollack, Ethan (Box 3)
- "All Politics is Local -- Even the Politics of War", 2010; Rotbart, Matthew V. (Box 3)
- "The Financial Geography of the Presidency: 1992-2008", 2010; Schillawski, Michael J. (Box 3)
- "Financial Crises and the Expansion of Executive Power in the United States", 2010; Smith, Daniel J. (Box 3)
- "Transitional Justice: A Comparative and Theoretical Analysis", 2010; Song, Harin C. (Box 4)
- "Rethinking Constitutional Precommitment: Imagining An American Nation in the Name of the People", 2010; Waldron, Brett Michael (Box 4)
- "Income Inequality, Firearm Availablility and Homicide Rates: A New Conception of the 'More Guns, More Murder' Argument", 2011; Bader, Gillian (Box 4)
- "How 'Originalist' Were the Original Supreme Court Justices?", 2011; Bartlett, Bradley (Box 4)
- "The Emergence of Maverick Supreme Court Justices", 2011; Cederoth, Theresa (Box 4)
- "Same-Sex Marriage and the Limits of Liberalism", 2011; Clemente, Matthew (Box 4)
- "Transitioning Autocrats: Why do Democratic Institutions Fail to Prevent Personal Integrity Violations in Anocracies?", 2011; Crowell, James (Box 4)
- "A Defense of United States Sanctions on Burma", 2011; Drucker, Mitchell (Box 4)
- "Chinese Oil and American Militarization in Africa", 2011; Eisenberg, Ross (Box 4)
- "Obscenity 2.0? Internet Pornography and the Development of Contemporary Community Standards", 2011; Faldermeyer, Andrea (Box 4)
- "Pakistan: The Islamic Republic for Some", 2011; Hussain, Ali (Box 4)
- "Race to the Top: Allocating Federal Education Funding Under the Obama Administration", 2011; Kim, Christine (Box 4)
- "Strangers in Eretz Yisrael: The Ordeal of Migrant Workers in Israel" (never received), 2011; Kwan, Esther (Box 4)
- "Judicial Review in Political Context: Korea and Japan", 2011; Lee, Minkyung (Box 4)
- "American Higher Education in Qatar: Causes and Consequences of the Rise of Satellite Campuses", 2011; Miller, Allen (Box 4)
- "End of Informal Empire: The Decline of United States Hegemony in Latin America Under the Bush Administration", 2011; Moreno, Elena (Box 4)
- "From Soup Kitchens to Soap Boxes: The Relationship Between Islamic Charities and Civic Involvement in Jordan", 2011; Morisy, Kathryn (Box 4)
- "What Can You Do For Me? Economic Asymmetry and Bargaining in Economic Transition of Reunified States: Comparing Germany and Vietnam", 2011; Park, Bora (Box 4)
- "Atoms for More Atoms: The Proliferation Inducing Potential of Peaceful Nuclear Assistance", 2011; Pasha, Zain (Box 4)
- "Not Quite What They Were Hoping For: How Western Democracies Condition the Emergence and Persistance of Electoral Authoritarian Regimes", 2011; Richards, Rebecca (Box 4)
- "Corruption by Design in International Organizations", 2011; Rifkind, Kyle (Box 4)
- "A Case Study Analysis Regarding Variables that Lead to Suicide Terrorism in Asymmetric Warfare Involving a Terroist Organization", 2011; Sellars, Matthew (Box 4)
- "Structural Intelligence Reform in America: The Success of Goldwater-Nichols, the Failure of IRTPA, and a Proposal for Reform", 2011; Steinhauer Holden (Box 4)
- "Forcing Silence" How Militarized Drug Policy Compromises Freedom of the Press in Latin America", 2011; Strong, Kayla (Box 4)
- "Assessing the Interpretive Effects of the Canadian Federal and Provinicial Governments' Official Multiculturalism Policy on New Immigrants' Political Incorportaion Levels", 2011; Szirmak, Daniel (Box 4)
- "Divisive Primaries and the Independent Vote in United States Senate Elections: Moving the Debate Forward", 2011; Wasser, Jaon (Box 4)
- "From Chemical Warfare to Cybersecurity: A Comparative Study of United States Interest in 'Use-based' Arms Control", 2011; Woo, Ryan (Box 4)
- "Laid-Off State Workers and the Chinese State: Institutionalization of State- Society Relations through Social Security", 2011; Zhang, Emily (Box 4)
- "Strategic Politics within Federalism's Frameworks: What Post-Enron Delaware Corporate Law Reveals about 21st Century Federalism", 2011; Zhang, Michael (Box 4)
- "Realism Without Cynicism: Considering Reinhold Niebuhr Today", 2012; Bellin, Judah (Box 4)
- "American Dream Foreclosure: Evolution of U.S. Housing Policy from Dwelling Place to Welfare State", 2012; Bor, James (Box 4)
- "Europe's New Scapegoats: the Politics of Anti-Muslim Discourse in the Era of Integration", 2012; Clarke, Emma (Box 4)
- "Rethinking Explanations of Secessionist Attempts: A Multi-Method Approach", 2012; Collins, Anna (Box 4)
- "Singapore-Malaysia Relations and International Relations Theory", 2012; Deng, Charlotte (Box 5)
- "Play Nice with the New Kids: A Reassessment of Democratization's Impact on Interstate Conflict", 2012; Malone, Iris (Box 5)
- "The Link Between the New York Governorship and the United States Presidency", 2012; David McCarey (Box 5)
- "Broadcast Deregulation and the Growth of Political Talk Radio", 2012; Murdter, David (Box 5)
- "The Dictator's Playbook: A path-dependent approach to authoritarian protest control policies in the Middle East", 2012; Panter, Jonathan (Box 5)
- "Engendering Justice? Male and Female Judges and Partisan Dynamics on the Federal Appellate Courts", 2012; Perkins, Kathleen E. (Box 5)
- "The Business of War: How U.S. Business Reacts to War Since the 20th Century", 2012; Taskin, Rahman (Box 5)
- "The Consequences of Incorporation: Reform and Heightened Coup Risk in Bolivia", 2012; Rhodin, Erica (Box 5)
- "Censorship and Self-Censorship: China's Influence on Academic Publishing in Hong Kong and Singapore", 2012; Schwartz, Laura Anne (Box 5)
- "Electoral Competition, Inequality, and Corruption in the Russian Federation: A Cross-Regional Analysis", 2012; Zimmerman, Katherine Anne (Box 5)
- “The Veterans Health Administration: Analyzing the Infrastructure Behind Success”, 2013; Boudreau, Emily (Box 5)
- “Essentialism and Right-wing Populism in the Tea Party: An Analysis of the Tea Party in the Context of the American Right”, 2013; Chan, Colin (Box 5)
- “The Rise and Fall of Latin American Liberation Theology: The Catholic Church and Progressive Organizing under Authoritarianism”, 2013; Collins, Nicole (Box 5)
- “Ain’t too proud to beg: IMF stabilization programs and incumbent reelection prospects”, 2013; Lucas, Bruno de Larragioti (Box 5)
- “Are You a Supreme Court Justice: An Analysis of the Ideological Interdependence between the Supreme Court and the Public”, 2013; Doshi, Samir (Box 5)
- “Privatized Peace? How Private Military and Security Companies May Shape the Future of United Nations Peacekeeping”, 2013; Glickman, Aaron (Box 5)
- "The French Presidential Elections of 2012: Memory, Communication, and National Identity”, 2013; Greenberg, Sarah (Box 5)
- “Asian American Electoral Strategy: Racialized and Deracialized Methods in California State Assembly Campaigns”, 2013; Huynh, Cindy (Box 5)
- “National Identity and Normativity in Egyptian and American Constitutionalism”, 2013; Rafanelli, Lucia (Box 5)
- “Economic Thought and American Political Development: From Franklin Roosevelt to Barack Obama”, 2013; Santana, Andrew D. (Box 5)
- “Resistance ǀ Identity ǀ Liberation: The East Timor and Aceh Conflicts in a Postcolonial Frame”, 2013; Schorr, Lauren Davis (Box 5)
- “How Micro-Targeting Shapes Political Knowledge”, 2013; Wu, Joyce (Box 5)
- “Authoritarian Cyberspaces: Regional Politics and the Internet in Russia and China”, 2014; Doherty, Tucker (Box 5)
- “A Vote of Confidence: Retrospective Voting in Africa”, 2014; Ellis, Erin (Box 5)
- “Let the Punishment Fit the Crime: A Study of Current Practices and Legal Strategies for Enforcing Human Trafficking Laws in Advanced Democracies”, 2014; Emberton, Caroline (Box 5)
- “Voting Under Siege: How Liberalism Frames the Franchise”, 2014; Henry, Margaret (Box 5)
- “What's the Matter with Hungary: Post-Accession Hungary and the Breakdown of Democracy”, 2014; Jakli, Laura (Box 5)
- “The Makings of Monetary Orthodoxy: The Political Economy of Central Bank Independence”, 2014; Reddy, Srinath Kethireddy (Box 5)
- “Flexibility in Orthodoxy: The Misunderstood Role of Wahhabi Ideology in Preserving the Saudi State”, 2014; Kuhn, Samuel (Box 5)
- “Confronting the Alien: Immigration Policy and Racial Formation in the United States in 1882, 1924, and 1965”, 2014; Rho, Sohee (Box 5)
- “Political Sacrilege: The American Catholic Bishops, Catholic Politicians in the Democratic Party and the Politics of Abortion”, 2014; Ryan, William (Box 5)
- “Constructing Justice: Constitutional Court Architecture in Nascent Democracies”, 2014; Schifrin, Aaron (Box 5)
- “The Journey or the Destination: Relative Impacts of Income Change and Current Income on Policy Preferences”, 2014; Silver-Fagan, Russell (Box 5)
- “Microfinance Amidst Meltdown: An Inquiry into the role of International Capital Markets in Determining Outcomes for National Microfinance Sectors during the Global Financial Crisis 2008”, 2014; Singh, Kirat (Box 5)
- “Building a Nation Under Siege: How the Second Chechen War Enabled Centralization and Authoritarianism in Putin's Russia”, 2014; Spencer, Christopher (Box 5)
- “Filling a Vacancy: Chicago Communities in Foreclosure”, 2014; Steele, Merritt (Box 5)
- “Panda or Tiger? A New Perspective on Recent Chinese Assertiveness”, 2014; Valette, Zoe (Box 5)
- "From the Ground Up: Building the GCC Labor Force”, 2015; Augenstein, Erica (Box 6)
- "Leading the Blind: How Peer Influence Keeps Voters Loyal and Allows Polarization to Grow”, 2015; Byers, Daniel (Box 6)
- "Assessing the Nature of Change: The Supreme Court and Juvenile Sentencing”, 2015; Herlitz-Ferguson, Bianca (Box 6)
- "Reshaping the Perspective: A Comparative Study of Long-term Peace in Croatia and East Timor”, 2015; Hwant, Haejin (Box 6)
- "Policy and Posterity: The Intersection of Intergenerational Justice and Public Policy in the United States”, 2015; Kim, Christina (Box 6)
- "The Theater of War: Presidential Initiative and Congressional Authorizations for Use of Military Force”, 2015; Lee, Justin (Box 6)
- "Between Political Institutionalization and Informality-Anti-corruption Enforcement in China since the 1990s”, 2015; Li, Jiali (Box 6)
- "A Thorough Examination of the Chinese Welfare System followed by Proposals for Changes based on European Experiences”, 2015; Li, Shourou (Box 6)
- "Change Preempted: Barack Obama's Untimely Liberal Rendezvous with a Conservative Political Time, 2015; Looi, Terence (Box 6)
- "Protective Propensities: Partisan and Ideological Polarization in the Regulatory Implementation of Trade Protection”, 2015; Matos, Roberto (Box 6)
- "Riding Which Wave? Responsiveness and Political Messaging in 2010 Gubernatorial Campaigns”, 2015; Melly, David (Box 6)
- "This is Ireland, And So Is That - A Study of the Relationship between State Structure and Violence in 20th Century Ireland", 2016; Alter, Michael (Box 6)
- "The Race of Life - Race and Citizenship in American Political Thought", 2016; Chung, Jinney (Box 6)
- "Addressing Climate Change: When Do Public-Private Partnerships Succeed?", 2016; Crowley, Chad (Box 6)
- "Defining the Boundary - Immigration, Peoplehood, and the Chinese Exclusion Act of 1882", 2016; Du, Yiran (Box 6)